in my beautiful slice of the cloud hello
people hello people where are the people
doing something know what you're all
doing make this or people maybe there's
no people if there's no people then
there's no stream oh there's a person I
was not Demi hi my love Wow okay wow
it's a little creepy oh we got one
viewer that's a little Oh about we got
we got oh we got eight off inch we got a
name that's in black that I can't read
that's poorly designed
hello risky banana thank you for
subscribing to my stream I'm so happy to
have you here welcome everybody welcome
welcome welcome happy fourth of July
look that 3d just went off alright so I
decided halfway through cooking to do a
cooking stream so student my
awkward like xok do not have my handlers
tell me how to drink a cup of water yes
yes they briefed me today that normal
Americans drink blood light and that's
why this stream is brought to you by Bud
Light
it's made with corn syrup yeah Bud Light
it's made with corn syrup perfect I love
points here there's nothing more
American than corn no that's that's
perfect no no no no we're not you're not
smoking meat we made portobello
mushrooms and like this already happened
so you missed the garlic mincing you mix
the mixing of balsamic vinegar and olive
oil
you missed skipping the rest of these
ingredients because I thought they were
stupid whoa whoa director homeless say
good things about Bud Light that's what
his jeans brought to you by brought you
by Bud Light made with corn syrup thank
you Thank You Al Aqsa thank you for
liking my apartment this
sometime we come out on my beautiful
balcony out here uh and we lay back down
and we just you know the world is ours
right cuz cuz I live in the cloud my bed
my bad I sleep out here I sleep out on
the porch yo I've been out that Valley
you ain't been up off that porch man
can't nobody tell me not this speaking
of the cloud um
oh no dots oh you got me bros what do I
make of all the cloud outages I think
Google and Facebook a full of
alright so we are cooking on this stream
so we already cooked these portobello
mushrooms I'm not really know where to
put the phone that you guys would be
able to see it alright so let's get a
bowl we're gonna be slicing some
Tomatoes here's a bill all right we're
gonna my cooking knife here I was
kidding about the cooking all right
we're like we're really cooking look at
these Tomatoes these are tomatoes on the
vine from Whole Foods you pay an extra
dollar to put them on the vine but guys
we broke the daily Eon sales record all
thanks to I think it was toast 69 that
came through at the last minute or it
was toast mister toast on discard if I'm
saying your name wrong I'm sorry I don't
have discord on my phone but we broke
the sales record today and in honor of
that we're doing a cooking stream
alright so this is a tomato we're gonna
wash it and then we're gonna try to make
some really nice burger slices for it I
guess you guys want to see the washing
of the tomato yeah
alright we're washing the today
all right I think it's good and watching
that tomato's didn't want very cool all
right
let's let's let's try to get that slice
to be really nice you know no no the
knife is pretty sharp why do you think
my knifes not sharpen my knife is gonna
cut through this leg butter what does
Gordon Ramsay say he says just let the
knife do the work we're just gonna let
the knife do the work we're just gonna
let the knife do the work yes
what's that tomato oh look at that slice
see this part of tomato it's not useable
on a burger just eat it
yep how can you do all right I really
want that slice to be the perfect burger
you know we were trying to make the
perfect burger here
you got that slice on your burger would
you be happy no no you made it sport
it's good you're just not letting the
knife do the work
just let the knife do the work yeah
there we go perfect and beautiful slices
slice this guy and it's trying to deform
and not become a tomato anymore I don't
know how Gordon Ramsay deals with that
all right we got some beautiful tomato
slices it'll be great for burgers I'm
gonna need a few more that's not a slice
help one more tomato huh
[Music]
so I haven't taken wall to the fridge
with me we're gonna get a splash of
olive oil in in a minute so we got the
oven preheated here for our portobello
mushrooms which were prepared off stream
we have a bit more balsamic olive oil
mixture a little bit heavy on the oil
and we're gonna we're gonna just drizzle
it we're gonna we're gonna put this guy
right here we're just gonna drizzle it
over these mushrooms yeah we're just
gonna get on that mushroom yeah get a
little bit on that mushroom offices this
is this is perfect guys yep just get a
little bit on this mushroom it did say
to marinate them and let them sit for 15
minutes so we're just gonna do that
because the people are coming over at
7:00 and that's who this Fiesta feast
has to be be be ready for yeah those
portobello mushrooms are gonna be sick
right all right so we got our Bud Light
here ready blog light number two let me
bring you guys to the fridge the fridge
is a really important part of cooking
yeah so we got got cooking right here
and we're gonna gonna bring you guys
back over here and we're just gonna
crack open this Bud Light cuz I'm from
New Jersey made with corn syrup the true
American sugar periscope had a better
chat interface I cut myself a little on
a camera oh well we're good let's just
wash my hands oh we've got to wash your
hands when you're cooking always just
put the soap on there like that just go
in and wash my hands up like this yup
there we go
make sure your hands are real clean
always real clean real clean get them
Germans off don't just wash with cold
water you gotta wash it with warm water
guys make sure to wash your hands with
warm water all right just dry my hands
on this dish towel over here perfect
okay let's get back to slicing Tomatoes
yes Johnny ma'am and this is cooking
stream oh that's a beautiful slice
there's gonna eat that slice there hmm
mmm not tomato is that's a delicious
tomato don't know where to make that
tomato better a little bit of olive oil
I'm gonna make the tomato slices pretty
then don't want overly thick tomato
slices perfect that's a good amount of
tomato for our burgers maybe we'll do
one more tomato slice right here
that's a thin tomato slice this tomato
slices miss shapen you know what we're
gonna do with the MS shape and tomato
slice guys we're gonna put it down the
disposal good view on that disposal
there yeah there we go
turn the water on always show the water
on for the disposal and that's the
mantle slice nobody will ever know about
because it was a UH it was bad tomato
that's right you gotta have that iceberg
lettuce the kind they put the Italian
salads you know what I'm talking about
okay what about the hey no shirt on
today I on this stream we hit a new
record today so I'm working hard I'm
gonna slice you all I'm gonna get bad
for Twitter saying that tech companies
really got the bands in full effect
these days everyone's getting bang on I
think they just banned people for
posting hacking content on YouTube I
don't know what am i content we can
consider hacking content who knows man
the thought police are coming for you
drink blood light that's made with corn
syrup and we don't how Bud Light would
feel about me saying cuz it's fake news
but it's so blessed shield for their
product and it makes a reference to an
ad campaign that everybody probably saw
I'm bleeding again this is terrible
I do that myself
earlier let's just wait a little bit to
stop bleeding
maybe we'll meditate on our beautiful
outside porch I live in the cloud who
thinks I was hot for South but after you
smoke enough weed you just kind of can
like turn it on and off you know no we
don't have any bandits we're just gonna
will my cut to heal I'm gonna will it to
heal okay
told you over the ledge it was my
beautiful iPhone 8 I was rich long
before a 16z don't smoke weed much
anymore
no I have drank one and a half Bud
Lights
but that's about it well no I cut myself
earlier and then the can crushing just
reopened my cut so we're gonna be a
little bit patient while it clots you
know it's got a clot maybe maybe if we
drink milk the blood will clot you know
what let's have a vitamin that's a great
way to make your blood clot I read that
on the Internet
all right so let's just we got vitamins
right here we got vitamins no we're just
gonna take one of these vitamins it's
been a while since I've seen Marc
Andreessen they don't talk to me anymore
they don't like me
delicious vitamin comes with everything
you need all these things alright I
think my bleeding stopped thanks to the
blood clotting power of vitamins
protectors disrupt okay so I'll tell you
the truth about tech our system director
all of us um you do a Department to it
later after cooking because this is a
cooking string by as I promised um I
went to it I was sorry my sister week
before TechCrunch Disrupt and I said
what I really wanted to do was pull my
pants down and like you know on the
stage right because that's effectively
what everybody there is doing but
they're not honest about it
right like they're just talking
right like why don't they just actually
you know drop trou and go for it
um so I tried to do that as best as I
could verbally
I saw your talk I K tonight to smoke and
not to drink
if you drink smoke anything will you get
to where you are now don't drink to
excess don't smoke to access if you're
the kind of person who smokes every day
and sits on the couch and does nothing I
think it was man I think it really was
like there's some weird theories about
what really happened
there's no the winners right history
right thank you thank you everybody life
to jailbreak the simulation talk okay I
believe the bleeding has now stopped
yeah we're good good thanks to the
clotting power of vitamins and we're
gonna get back to cooking alright so
when you get a hit list
you're going to make sure to wash that
lettuce really well because lettuce
that's not washed well can become gross
okay I'm still bleeding we gotta wait we
gotta wait guys we gotta look just stop
oh all right let's look at it up can I
show you guys this is this against which
this policy am I gonna get banned by the
way could you guys subscribe pour salt
on it all right let's try that and we're
in the middle of a cooking stream after
all so let's let's try putting some salt
on the wound is that a good idea it's
not like a bad ion let's say can't show
blood on stream I'm gonna get bad we
salted it oh yeah we put salt in that
yeah Zak does that work I probably
should have googled this before I just
listen to you guys
daughter less your Bach I don't know
what else did I mention
did I mention crime and punishment about
why I'll never be a criminal why do you
know where the column AI offices that's
concerning what are we cooking we're
making burgers we're making burgers just
like Gordon Ramsay will also make it
some portobello mushrooms okay if I
stand stream whatever I want
and be entertained while doing it then
there's no point having streaming career
like look if I have to be the kind of
streamer where it's like you know tits
or gtfo that's not the kind of stream
where I want to be okay okay I've had it
with this bleeding it's really starting
to piss me off now we're just gonna wrap
it up I'm gonna wrap it up with a little
little little tourniquet right here by
the way I just want to make clear and I
didn't cut myself with a knife I cut
myself earlier and then reopened by
wound when trying to crush a can of Bud
Light made with corn syrup we got that
wound wrapped up that's right yeah
putting salt in your wound there's also
a saying called Dobby bitch and that's a
saying that I try to
all right cool let's watch this lettuce
gonna show you guys washing the lettuce
[Music]
we're gonna wash the lettuce together
everybody will wash and let us alright
cool so I'm gonna want to let us this
cold water not with warm water
wait who is that cheese portobello
mushroom I'm a way sicker portobello
mushrooms
oh then Gordon Rambler and he's a good
cook ma'am all right so I don't really
know how you prepare a lettuce but let's
just try eating a lettuce and see what
happens okay
ayo eat crap do not wash yet oh we got
the leaf now we do this to leave
all right guys I'm gonna do with that
whatever I don't like that way the stuff
that goes in the disposal anything I
don't wipe I just put in the disposal oh
[Applause]
that's gonna leave you guys out of good
Middle East and we got this for later
plug this back in the fridge oh cool all
right
now let's just put the leaps to this
bowl right here and let's wash up always
watch everything guys you don't know
where your produce has been he's gotta
wash your produce just wash good yo you
know what I can't believe 132 people are
watching this like I get it when
you guys watch the program I'm actually
pretty good at that but I don't think
this is how you're supposed to do
lettuce at all the bleeding stopped
where's the clotting not working we have
to take them inviting me
mostly stop we'll wait a little bit more
mmm all right cool lettuce is so cheap
go ham for you guys I made some chips
fill my chip want to check you guys on
chip
but like maybe the point zero
antiperspirant we could try that all
right so much people do something on
credit uh so I think we're good on
beliefs here we're actually gonna
transfer the Leafs over a small bowl
here lettuce is cheap we could have done
more lettuce I think we cheaped out a
little bit on the lettuce but washing
lettuce actually takes a lot of time oh
okay all right
my bulbs I used one for that I use one
for that we're just gonna use a plate
guys a little bit red onion right here
kept it in a bag wash the onion that's
sure you guys watching the onion
all right cool watching the onion yeah I
missed the keyboard sound to the chat
you posted on Instagram isn't the one
you use oh yeah
I bought a new chair cuz I'm rich make
sure to tell you know I wanted Instagram
there all right cool
I love telling people on Instagram that
I'm rich we're gonna really slice this
onion good it's a good slice I'll look
at that beautiful look at that beautiful
slice can't believe that look at that
that's an incredible looking slice um
we're just gonna peel off this outer oh
that's actually where's chop this
alright
good shot right like that that's a
beautiful piece of onion for the burger
if I got that cut on you know my burger
I'd be very happy all right cool I'm
gonna move the tomatoes out to the plate
as well I'm gonna put them on the plate
here you're gonna arrange it like we
like you know did something I cool look
at this we're gonna show you guys this
plate when we're done we're gonna put
the letters on the plate too oh yeah
well this this looks like Gordon Ramsay
made yeah look at this plate so far
that's like that's a nice plate of off
things to put on your burger let's just
slice a few more onions and I think
we're good all right people suffocate
eating that slice you know how I feel
don't know
you know people never onion right here
we're gonna just slice this onion off
right down here
oh no look that slice didn't come out
well when did it turn into little onion
we're really gonna try to spice it super
well so my salary that Gordon Ramsay
knows some trick that I don't not so
good-looking slice cool yeah you really
really got to look tonight through the
work here perfect
oh that that's a good slice we'll just
put it back together here no one will
know that I'm a terrible chef right
that's a nice looking on you all right
I'll just put that right over there all
right we making burgers right here on
this dream if you just joined us welcome
this is the Geo hot Channel well we cook
cooking alright this I am NOT putting it
bad beautiful later
that's good but white guys alright we're
good on the onion now let's get the only
part of the burger than anybody cares
about first we're gonna do a little bit
of googling for how to season your
burger meat so let's go over here to the
computer here we are on the computer
where we looked up baked portobello
mushrooms and let's look up burger
seasoning yes burger meat seasoning okay
Oh Fuddruckers I see there when I was a
kid
bread yeah get this paprika
ground black pepper salt sugar garlic
powder onion powder green cayenne pepper
that's crazy that's crazy we're not
doing any of that we're gonna wash
our hands again just to show you guys
cuz hand washing extremes are really in
these days I just watch I mean imagine
that was just a stream of people washing
their hands you really got to get the
soap everywhere turn on that warm water
not cold we're just gonna wing it for
the seasoning we're just gonna wing it
okay all of em for pointing to you I
appreciate y'all sticking with me we're
getting ready to move on to the main
event where we bring out the meat
let's take a look well let me just do
what my seasoning play a little bit here
I've got some onion we got some letters
and we got some Tomatoes well that looks
oh that looks this looks I mean really
could go to any do a better job that's
what you want to look at this right
that's that's beautiful that's that's
that's food porn right there you guys
could could post that on reddit we've
got like seven likes perfect yeah I love
that love that I
let's see the chip let's block with John
oh why he hasn't we're touching the edge
of okay let's get out couple pounds of
meat and we got a blob light yeah we got
country natural beef right here I like
to leave the meat all things have innate
my cutting board that is a nice-looking
log of meat if I've ever seen one
oh yeah look at that put bottom on the
patty before cooking I like that that's
good best good tip alright let's just
make that much of it and we put the rest
away for later alright
this got the ball take this log of meat
throw it in this bowl here right wrap up
this to put back in the fridge just as
later food you always beat later food
guys don't eat all your food at once you
always need to save some food for later
I'm gonna watch a few more cooking shows
and I'm gonna imitate their like things
so well yeah when I say it's gonna be
ridiculous like you gotta have some
later food guys you know
[Music]
we're gonna use this on you we're gonna
mince it and we're gonna use this onion
I always like a little onion in my
burger as well as on my burger I'm a big
fan of onion let's just say all right
this one I don't think is really edible
the rest of them are so this one I don't
know not edible all right this one's all
good so let's just slice this up a bit I
can't watch the camera while I do this
because I do not want to top myself
already caught myself crushing a can of
Bud Lights which is made of coin serum
it's delicious oh yeah oh yeah that's
that's not satisfying oh that's really
satisfying guys that's really satisfying
let's just let's just cut up these
onions here oh yeah we're gonna have
we're gonna really mince this on all
right we want minced onion mix in with
our burger meat what's up with the face
what does that mean you never cook meat
so don't move
meeting all the ones don't look good hey
hey if you want to like me you know what
love this dream right now but if you do
like me please subscribe because this
good stream is only made possible by
subscribers like you
okay so we got the meat and we got honey
so we're just gonna you know mash this
meat down a little bit here gonna mash
this meat down and we're gonna take
these onions
all right cool we got some meat some
onions she's gonna be delicious you guys
we gotta look we gotta figure out
I knew the onions we gotta figure out
what else we have to put it in we're
gonna put in a little bit of garlic we
might do a little bit of garlic
okay two teaspoons of paprika I don't
have that one way to have teaspoons
of ground black pepper we can do that
one 1/4 teaspoons of salt what any sugar
in my oh we can throw a little
cayenne pepper right I think I might
happen they might actually have a whole
cayenne pepper but that might be a
little much garlic overdoing the spice
rack here see what we have we have cumin
I don't know what that is we have
oregano we have chili powder
that's not cayenne pepper powder and we
have cinnamon mmm I'll take the pepper
out definitely pepper always pepper
let's just use salt and pepper and onion
that's that's perfect that's perfect
recipe for my burgers not using any
cinnamon not making weird burgers you
guys all right a little bit of pepper a
little bit of salt and then let's just
grind this up here I'm sorry I dropped
y'all I just touch the meat so I'm just
gonna wipe my hands on that and then put
you guys back up all right we're good
let's just mix this up here that's some
onions in here got some pepper and we
got some sauce we can always add a
little bit more pepper and salt say this
is actually a lot of meat I love a
little bit of onion
and with my me we might have gone a
little overboard on the onion so it
seemed like a lot of onions so we're
just going to take these onions and
we're going to throw them in the sink
that's perfect yeah now we didn't go
overboard on the onion anymore
we're good we're good we're good I'm
just gonna rinse my hands off a little
bit wipe them on this flower sack right
here and we're gonna go ahead and add a
little bit more salt and add a little
bit more pepper
all right cool cool cool cool all right
that looks good no it's good that let's
just let's just keep going with this
just really really get this meat get
this meeting in tip-top shape here you
know what I'm gonna add the rest of the
meat if we're going we're not gonna save
any food for later I know I said we were
going to but we're just not gonna do
that
not out of your neck you stop with your
stupid suggestions so in order to
balance that out you just take another
ball of meat and you're throwing in the
other ball of meat and you just mush
that all together there that's all gonna
come together and form a beautiful you
know great consistency
burger burger meat stew here this looks
this looks like exactly what you're
gonna want to make make burgers out of
we're gonna break it up into burgers in
a minute get the cutting board out
really uh break it up into burgers do we
need more salt and pepper I'm gonna
leave that up to you guys yeah yeah
onion salt pepper me what this great
you guys know I would don't let the
song pepper all right all right I hear
you I hear you okay okay okay all right
we're done with the salt and pepper okay
well I hope more salt and pepper later
right perfect all right yeah all right
the meats already perfect as it is
that's what you always tell me all right
and egg and breadcrumb stuff
no we're not doing any of that I'll get
our cutting board right here let's just
wipe it off yeah perfect
well give it a little rinse and then
we're gonna break the rule putting meat
on the cutting board but I don't notice
how else to make good patties such that
y'all can see all right perfect
all right so I don't know my you know my
milligram scale I got rid of that when I
stopped doing drugs so we're just like
afraid we're just gonna take a ball here
and this is going to become patty I
think it's not a good patty sighs it's a
little large well does it actually more
meat than I thought is that gonna make
it good let's just I've seen like you
make like a ball is that like a good
patty it might be it might even be a
little bit thick okay
really if the only thing I know about me
is quarter pounder with cheese so maybe
we want like something that big looks
like it's gonna be a good patty you guys
this is too big this is too big
I don't know patty says looks good I
perfect right yeah we got one all right
they're good all right let's just take
the rest of this meat put it back in
this bowl here and let's put this in the
fridge for later this is later all right
we're gonna take this and you're gonna
throw that away cause we don't need any
more all right now we get to the fun
part the part where we you know we're
cooking with wood stove go over to the
stove here you know and then we all use
cast iron pans one guy firebase and to
cast iron pans it's almost time to put
the portobello mushrooms into the oven I
want to make sure they're ready just in
time when my guests arrive at seven
o'clock so
let me figure out how to put you guys on
the stove give me one second how are we
gonna do this so here's what we got here
I'm just gonna give this a little bit of
heat and then we're gonna throw some
butter in it then we're gonna wipe it
down make sure that gaskets oh that
looks perfect
we only cook with cast iron in this
house B of this cast iron pan and this
cast iron pan
I'm not frying the mushrooms we're
actually gonna stove the mushrooms I
know it's a little bit controversial but
we're gonna go with the stove so the
mushrooms actually put oil in the pan
all right so what are we gonna fry with
we're gonna fry with olive oil and we're
gonna fry we thing we're gonna fry with
the butter okay just patty you're way
too thick you're with me we're
splitting this into two bags you're
doing patty with this will do patty out
with my Patty spin olive oil smokes
earlier okay all right money baby thick
Novik is hard to cook I've done this
before
no I have heard that olive oil smoked it
has a smoke point oh my god where the
chat go Shh twitch interface is terrible
I know I got ya I got y'all show chat
having an actual streamer interaction
yes welcome to the gorge hot stream
thank you for subscribing by the way I
really appreciate everybody with a star
you're better people than other people
you guys all deserve a Bud Light if I
could send a Bud Light to you right now
I would not like really but please
subscribe if you haven't subscribed
because it's your subscriptions that
make my dream of being a cam girl
possible wait F wait what mister you
broke now what we get to stick Wi-Fi in
this apartment
alright we heating up this pan here a
little bit we're just gonna throw a
little bit of butter in there you got
the nicest Irish hairy gold butter
butter has a higher smoke point than
olive oil I do watch cooking shows once
just gonna take a slab of butter here
cut that butter in half and take some
butter throw it in the pan now that
looks perfect
oh that looks Alex ideal alright it's
gonna take that I got to show you guys
this this looks mad cool take that
butter we're just gonna move it around a
little bit here to really get that get
that pan at that pan ready go ready to
cook my burger here alright alright a
low battery oh not regular butter oh we
got regular butter alright alright you
got we got a back going on there now
we're just gonna take our pre-prepared
burger patty I'm gonna throw it in the
bar all right good I don't think it's
too thick guys I think you over
with me I'm gonna I'm gonna actually
flip the stream around so we can use
this camera that's perfect oh yeah look
at that look at that burger press down
on the center okay
all right that looks great
my means to big bunkers I've told you
all right there my spatula smack them
with a spatula okay all right all right
well push it down with this guy oh yeah
look at that sizzling oh look at that
look at that beautiful plastic spatula
imprint right there this is what America
is all about
if you can't get behind America and get
off the street because this is really
this is truly the American dream right
here I live in this beautiful cloud and
I'm talking to 127 people on the
internet and we're making burgers
wait it's not time to flip it yet don't
with me all right
low to medium heat oh then we're gonna
lower the heat a little bit here got to
lower the heat because it's so thick oh
yeah and I bought some healthy
multigrain bottles because I don't like
to really eat bread um carbs are bad for
you okay
it's 6:30 so maybe we'll give it another
5 minutes and then we'll put these
portobello mushrooms in the oven this
burger a little bit of time to sizzle
here how do I know when it's ready to
flip I already put I put tons of I put
tons of butter
hey if Google steals my burger methods
you know Larry and Sergey if you ever
want to come over for a burger you're
welcome to don't invite sundar Pichai
that's all I'm saying
I almost made it help me help you joke
on Twitter today I was a Logan Paul fan
briefly
all right I'm starving fresh
I really flip the burger is it time to
flip they say you're only supposed to
flip it once I know that from the Gordon
Ramsay strings so let's just I don't
know how to hold you all right let's
just open up this just got to make sure
the Bud Light logo is really in there
that's perfect let's just get out one of
these it's a good-looking fun fun
actually dad oh that plate I got a plate
and we're just gonna go one on the plate
just looks sad totally strap on a little
bit I don't have a toaster so that's too
bad alright is it time to flip the
burger guys
should we flip it come on you asked
where I was a Logan puffin hey man
somebody needed to support that guy
after the suicide forest video he came
back and became a bitch I didn't support
him anymore but during the month heated
in the stream I was the biggest Logan
Paul fan okay perfect let's flip the
burger guys oh oh look at that looks
like perfection what Paul has a podcast
now the answer is not this better look
sick what are you all talking about I
don't like Mayo Mayo is disgusting
we're killing it I think we're killing
the burger game here get rid of this
you only think that oh that's
like the burger juices and stuff that's
just gonna make the second burger be
even better this is my test burger
before the guests arrive I'll put a
piece of butter on top of the burger all
right we're gonna do that we're gonna
trust you man let's get the butter out
let's just take a little piece of butter
here and let's just throw it on top of
the burger you think that's gonna be
good it's a holiday
we can eat saturated fat saturated fats
I don't know really not bad they are for
you but carbs carbs make me tired and
that's why we're eating whole wheat buns
I wish I could eat them up with a little
bit bell but that's not even gonna
happen all right shut the bar brother in
the burger now this is too much guys I'm
get rid of that butters going over there
I don't want to anymore all right I
think this burger might be done is it
done it might be pretty good to me
is it done char the bone on the stove
she told a mad man that in there for a
minute you're saying okay it's not done
yet all right we'll put it back we'll
put it back all right I hear you I hear
you all right all right it's back
burgers back burgers back don't worry no
I'm done no harm done but you got to
wait for the juice to start coming out
the top well how am I gonna know that
the middle is still raw okay great all
right all right how patient do I have to
be I'm a really impatient guys drink
called life
wait staff knows geo hot am I gonna get
the end for cooking it's cooking allowed
I don't know butter the bun and brown it
on the stove no no we're not cooking the
bun guys that's too much all right put a
slice of cheese on top we're not making
a cheese burger here we're making a
hamburger cheese is like carbs all right
is it done
no maybe not actually it doesn't look
that cooked
I'm not putting cheese on a
burger okay oh yeah I have a little bit
worried that when I said this party had
mushrooms people maybe thought that they
were the other kind of mushrooms
wouldn't have any of those mushrooms
here we only have these mushrooms there
should talk no there are portobello
mushrooms I know my cooking's all right
let's put this in the oven let's do it
let's do it let's go oven guys it's oven
time all right we cook them for 15
minutes
perfect right this has got to be done is
this done yet no actually maybe not I
don't have any American cheese guys I
got a bag with some cheddar in it I got
one mozzarella
yeah mozzarella we got no the guests can
have cheese I'm just not a me any cheese
just burgers for me it's a fat burger
that's what I'm talking about right not
putting any mozzarella cheese on the
verb Oh
yeah alright alright alright I skipped
out in the American cheese
I went cheap I didn't buy something it
was very own American of me I'm Way too
minimalist for America anyway I should
buy way more things and we're gonna get
right on that
after we drink a few more Bud Lights oh
can I describe the snow all the smell is
where the smell is it's really
intoxicating guys that's a fat burger
this actually looks really good you put
a little beer on the burger we're gonna
do that talk about beer burgers we'll
season it a little perfect oh yeah look
at that
yeah oh that looks good I just turn this
fan on up here oh yeah the old pod light
we're not putting it in the oven
terrible alright alright looks good it
actually looks genuinely delicious I
don't know how to tell what it's done
you think it's ready Al Aqsa alright the
locks of things it's ready can I get a
little more support on taking the burger
off the grill should we do it I
appreciate you all being with here being
with me here cooking all right hey hey
just wish you had this burgers you wish
you had this burger all right let's just
put it on the bun right here I'm gonna
move it over a little of my hands cuz
not that good with a spatula let's get
out these beautiful toppings that we
prepared earlier let's turn the heat off
over here let's turn the fan off over
here alright now what do you like on
your burger I like a bit of raw red
onion let's just throw that on top right
there can I slice a tomato oh that looks
great and let's throw on some letters I
love letters I'll look this letters is a
thick letters it's gonna be delicious on
my burger I'll put it on this side of
the bun here and we don't eat it with
ketchup or Mayo cuz that's just
disgusting alright that looks great
that looks great oh look at that burger
got a whole wheat bun right there
healthy no carb
uh yes yes guys yes we did it we made
this burger Five Guys Burgers and Fries
right here
remember Zoe Quinn it's actually really
good it's delicious
that was the best thing I thought in a
long time the bun could use a little bit
of heating up but this patty this patty
is the epitome of excellence oh my god
that just tastes so good my guests are
gonna be thrilled with quality and these
burgers I feel like such a success right
now you know we went through a bit of a
rough patch last weekend where I was
feeling like a failure
but as you can all see them comma a
guy's Twitter sales have increased
exponentially we're gonna be so bad you
know what it we're doing
advertising we're selling out but sell
out man let's sell out boys was still
out was buy a jet ski all the beer the
beer no what made his burger so good mmm
mmm who's that my burger wasn't juicy I
could imagine a bear burger that is
cooked medium-rare to perfection
[Music]
mmm-hmm that's so good that's that's
delicious
that is truly oh there's no seats like I
made a list of what I had at my
apartment and I said if you want
anything else you gotta bring yourself
that's what minimalists here oh I should
make burgers more often mmm no I love
this fat burger you gotta be totally
right about not trying to double patty
this we went with one thick patty
with all your help we were patient
imagine I'd taken it off the stove
earlier on imagine I took it off the
stove and didn't put it back we'd be in
serious trouble right now but thanks to
cooking with all of you guys on twitch
that burger is cooked to perfection mmm
I love America I'm so happy to be here
right now this is a true American
pastime drink a Bud Light make them
burgers with the bunch of borough's even
though you're virtual and think we have
six minutes all right well I'm gonna
have to go I'm gonna have to rewind the
twitch stream and figure out when I put
the portobello mushrooms in because it
did say 15 minutes people I told him to
show up at 7:00 so I'll probably show up
at 7:30 and I've already eaten probably
all the portobello mushrooms there so
problem this burger this burger has to
be one of the best things I've made in a
long time
I'm gonna savor just lastly I'll bite
for once we get off stream I really
appreciate having all of you here to
cook with me
that was absolutely delicious burger I'm
so happy to be in this wonderful country
well it's day of Independence
now the streams gotta go man streams
gotta go I got things to do
so Tommy eye-opener right I really I
think I can make a great burger
restaurant all right thank you all for
joining happy Independence Day guys have
a good one
hopefully you're making your own burgers
and if I ever sell out let me know it'd
be like George old you would have never
let you do that
and I'd be like yeah you're right and
then we'll fix it because if I go up to
be a sellout no matter what I have in my
life I failed but if I'm here with you
bros eatin delicious burgers in my
lovely apartment it really doesn't cost
that much money cuz I live in San Diego
now I'm very happy oh yeah follow me on
instagram one I'm 20 19 comment make
sure to follow me in there for them when
I meet girls you know it used to be like
yeah what's your phone number right and
like okay you die message no iMessage
now it's like what's your Instagram
right I like that I've 12,000 followers
I'd really like a blue checkmark if
somebody knows how to get me that blue
checkmark hide if you want like a favor
you get me a blue checkmark and I'll do
a favor for you thank you all for
joining blue checkmark
you